A Guide to the Joshua Lederberg personal papers, Subject File FA1087
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Subject File, 1
  - Japan - Hamamatsu Photonics (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Human Frontier Science Program, 1987 December 14-15 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Japan - Human Frontier Science Program - Japan - Tenative Minutes of the Second Meeting of the Feasibility Study Committee for the HFSP, 1987 December 14-15 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Human Frontier Science Program (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Human Frontier Science Program, 1988 February-1989 June (Box 14, Folder 19-20)
  - Lederberg Talk (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Japan Trip, 1987 February 7-14 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Japan - Human Frontier Science Program, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Japan - Human Frontier Science Program, 1987 December (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Japan - Human Frontier Science Program -, 1986-1987 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Japan - Human Frontier Science Program, 1987 November (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Japan - Human Frontier Science Program - (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Japan - Human Frontier Science Program - Research Grants, Fellowships and Workshops (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Japan - Human Frontier Science Program, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Japan - Human Frontier Science Program, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Japan - Proctor and Gamble, 1985, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Japan - Human Frontier Science Program, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Japan Trip (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Japan - Human Frontier Science Program (Box 15, Folder 1A)
  - Japan - Human Frontier Science Program, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 1B)
  - Japan-Research of Foreign Sc. (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Japan Say No (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Japan - Institute for Scientific Information (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - NAS and NSF - Japan (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Japan External Trade Organization (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - AIST - MITI (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Japan - MITI, 1983, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Japan, 1988 May-June, October (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Japan, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 10-12)
  - Lederberg letter to Edward Ames (Mary Flagler Cary Charitable Trust), 1988 November (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Japan, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Japan - US-Japan Legislators, Committee, 1989 May 5-8 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - National Institute of Health - Study Section, 1957-1958 (Box 15, Folder 15A)
  - Genetics Study Section, 1959 May 10-11 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - National Science Foundation, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - National Institute of Health - General Correspondence, 1958-1961 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - National Science Foundation, 1962-1964 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - National Science Foundation - Proposal Evaluations (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - National Science Foundation, 1957-1960 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - National Institute of Health - National Cancer Institute, 1980 December (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - National Cancer Institute (Dr. Vincent DeVita) (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - National Institute of Health, 1985-1990 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - National Institute of Heath - ADAMHA (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - National Institute of Health - Grant Applications (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - National Institute of Health - Fogarty International Program (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Job Applications - NIH (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Bernadine Healy, 1992 March 20 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - National Institute of Health, 1984-1986 (Box 15, Folder 30-31)
  - Organizational Change at NIH (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Publications from other sources (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Psychopharmacology (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Publications, Annoucements, Reprints (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI), 1978 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Re: E. Garfield, 1978 February 3 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Building "Project Goodlook", 1978 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Space, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI), 1977 May 10 (Box 16, Folder 9A)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI), 1976 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Henry Small papers (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Chronological, 1964-1975 (Box 16, Folder 12-38)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI), 1961 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Chronological, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 2-3)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Citation Index, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Garfield Reprints (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - ASCA (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Investment (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Lederberg Miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Financial Statements, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI), 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Management Review, 1987 July (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - ASCA, 1981-1983 (Box 17, Folder 12-14)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Atlas of Science (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI), 1981 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI), 1978-1979 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - 1980-1981 - ISI Alert (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Board Meeting, 1980 November 25 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Financial Statements, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI), 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 21-22)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Conference Call, 1982 December 2 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Board, 1982 September 28 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Science Citation Index - Obliteration (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - "Sleepers" Project, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Newspaper (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI), 1978-1981 (Box 17, Folder 28-35)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Primate, 1979 May (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Children's Day Care Development Project, 1980 October 27 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI), 1979 (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Financials, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Board Meeting, 1979 April 17 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 5-6)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI), 1978 June 8 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Minutes, 1978 October 13 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Financial Statement, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Dr. Eugene Garfield (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) (Box 18, Folder 11-12)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI), 1976 December 27 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI), 1976 June 9 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI), 1960 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI), 1962 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI), 1955-1959 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - ASCA, 1978, 1980-1981 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI), 1988-1992 (Box 18, Folder 19-27)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Board of Directors Meeting, 1990 June 27 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Board of Directors Meeting, 1988 February 2 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Board of Directors Meeting, 1989 May 25 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI), 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 31-32)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - ISI vs. AAAS (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - ASCA (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Review-Current Abstracts (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Board of Directors Meeting, 1991 July 31 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - CCOD Networking, 1991 January (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Board, 1990 June 27 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI), 1990 January 31 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Adv Meeting, 1990 April 16 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - R. S. Bramson, 1988 June (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Ted Cross (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Tom Ewing (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Board Meeting, 1989 May 25 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - G. G. (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Irv Sher (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Garfield, Eugene - Profile on Genetic Engineering (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI), 1985-1988 (Box 19, Folder 1-11)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Board of Directors, 1987 November 17 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Board of Directors, 1990 June 27 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Press Adv Board Meeting, 1985 October 28 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Board Meeting, 1990 December 20 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Adequacy of the Design of the Bibliographic Formatting System for Sci-Mate (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Aging and Intelligence (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - AI (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Atlas of Science (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Atlas of Science (Pharm) (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Biography (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Budget, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Caring Center (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Carroll Report (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Child Care Assistance Program (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - CD Editions (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - CCOD (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - CDE (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Current Comments, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Current Contents (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Citation Classics (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Classics at Office (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Contemporary Classics (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Shareholders, 1988 October 18 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - NAS Computer - IBM vs. Sperry (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Current Contents - ISI-NAS (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - NLM (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - ISI-NSF Controversy (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Merger (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Portfolio (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Press (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Primate (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Quality Control (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Science Advisory Board, 1986 July 25 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Science Advisory Board Directory (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Science Citation Index (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Science Newspaper (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Science (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - The Scientist (Box 19, Folder 50-54)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - The Scientist, 1986 June (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - The Scientist - Citation, Complaints (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - The Scientist - Lederberg's Comments (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - PAB Meeting Agenda (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Editorial, 1987 June 25 (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Science Week, 1982 April 1 (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Science Week, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Science Week-Chronicle, 1981-1987 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Science Observer (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Science Observer, 1985 September (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) - Irving Sher (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - New York City Partnership (NYCP), 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - New York City Partnership (NYCP), 1989-1990 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - New York City Partnership (NYCP) - Governor Kean and Cuomo, 1985 May 30 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - New York City Partnership (NYCP) - Hi-Tech (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - New York City Partnership (NYCP) - Breakfast Meeting, 1985 April 16 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - New York City Partnership (NYCP), 1985 January 16 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - New York City Partnership (NYCP) - Proposal to Establish a Regional Technology Development Organization for New York City (Enzo Project), 1985 August 20 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - New York City Partnership (NYCP) - Board of Directors Meeting, 1986 February 26 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - New York City Partnership (NYCP) - Kathryn Wylde - "New Homes" (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - New York City Partnership (NYCP) - Telecommunications (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - New York City Partnership (NYCP) - Health Care in NYCP (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - New York City Partnership (NYCP) - PPRC, 1986 September 12 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - New York City Partnership (NYCP) - Policy Committee Meeting, 1986 December 4 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - New York City Partnership (NYCP) - Annual Meeting of Members and Policy Committee Meeting, 1986 May 5 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - New York City Partnership (NYCP) - 1985 Partners Night, 1985 November 8 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - New York City Partnership (NYCP) - Meeting, 1986 April 22 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - New York City Partnership (NYCP) - Conference on Corporate Expansion in New York City, 1986 March 20 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - New York City Partnership (NYCP) - Conference - November 13, 1985 - Ty Incubator, 1985 November 13 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - New York City Partnership (NYCP) - High-Tech Committee Meeting, 1986 June 9 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - New York City Partnership (NYCP) - High-Tech Report for Annual Report, 1986 June 4 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - New York City Partnership (NYCP) - Financ. Services - June 4, 1986 - Sub Committee Meeting (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - New York City Partnership (NYCP) - National Innovations Workshop, 1987 September 18-19 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - New York City Partnership (NYCP) - Policy Committee Meeting, 1987 May 4 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - New York City Partnership (NYCP) - Project Planning and Review Commission, 1986 May 12 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - New York City Partnership (NYCP) - Policy Committee Meeting, 1987 December (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Comparative Costs of Doing Business in Seven Cities, JJ Studley Inc. (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Baer University-Industry (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - University Liscensing Association for Biotechnology (ULAB) (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - New York City Partnership (NYCP) (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - America's Competitive Challenge (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - New York City Partnership (NYCP), 1985 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - New York City Partnership (NYCP) - Business Higher Education Forum (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - OTA on University-Industry Relationship on West Coast (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - IBA Workshop of University-Industry Cooperation (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Urban Development Corporation Biotech Study - A D Little, 1984 July (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - New York City Partnership (NYCP) - Urban Development Corporation High Tech Adv Council (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Port Authority and Bio Tech - Fred Lehman, 1984 July 18 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - New York City Partnership (NYCP), 1984-1985 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - RPI Incubator Facility (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - New York City Partnership (NYCP), 1985 June 10 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Biotech Industrial Facility (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Urban Development Corporation, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - New York State Economic Forum (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Student Science Education - NYAS (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences (Box 21, Folder 9-10)
  - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences - Special Project (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences - Notes Toward a History, 1984 July (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences - Agenda and Minutes, 1984 January 12 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences - Agenda and Minutes, 1983 January 14 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences - Annual Reports (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences, 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 16-19)
  - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences - Calendar Dates (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences - Joshua Lederberg (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 22-23)
  - Annual Reviews Inc., 1981-1989 (Box 22, Folder 1-27)
  - Annual Reviews - Jack Hollander (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Annual Reviews - History (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Annual Reviews - Immunology (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Annual Reviews - International Security (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Annual Reviews - Nominating Committee (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Annual Reviews - Nutrition (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Annual Reviews - Physiology (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Annual Reviews - Public Health (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Annual Reviews (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Annual Reviews - Toxicology (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Annual Reviews - Wagner vs. Roman (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Annual Reviews - Editor Search (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Annual Reviews - Search Committee (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Annual Reviews (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Annual Reviews - Early History (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Annual Reviews - History (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Charles Babbage Institute, 1981-1988 (Box 22, Folder 44-47)
  - Charles Babbage Institute - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1979 October 5 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Charles Babbage Institute, 1983-1984 (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Charles Babbage Institute - Trustees and Board of Directors Meetings, 1988 October 4 (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Charles Babbage Institute - Trustees and Board of Directors Meetings, 1983 October 7, 1984 October 26 (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - Charles Babbage Institute - Annual Report, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Bionet, 1984-1985 (Box 22, Folder 53-54)
  - Biophoton (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - Carnegie Corporation, 1984-1989 (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
  - Carnegie Corporation - Board, 1989 April 20 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Carnegie Corporation - AV Nuclear War, 1989 January 18-19 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Carnegie Corporation - Middle Schools Program Life Sci Adv Board (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Carnegie Corporation - Board, 1989 March 23 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Carnegie Corporation - Science, Tech and Government (SAP), 1987 November 30 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Carnegie Corporation - Board - Staff Retreat, 1984 May 2-4 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Carnegie, 1985 June (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Carnegie Corporation - Human Biol Adv Board including Joshua Lederberg, 1987 September 14 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Carnegie Meeting Halfdan Mahler, 1988 May 23 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Carnegie Commission on Science Technology and Government (CSAP), 1989 (Box 23, Folder 12-16)
  - Carnegie Commission on Science Technology and Government (CSAP) - Washington DC, 1989 May 10 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Carnegie Commission on Science Technology and Government (CSAP) - Bruce Smith (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Carnegie Commission on Science Technology and Government (CSAP), 1989 November 1 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Carnegie Commission on Science Technology and Government (CSAP), 1989 August (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Carnegie Commission on Science Technology and Government (CSAP), 1988-1989 (Box 23, Folder 21-52)
  - Middle School Life Sciences Initiative - Report on Advisory Board Meeting, 1987 September (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) (Box 24, Folder 1-3)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) - CISAC (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) - CISAC - BW (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) - CISAC - Future of US-Soviet Nuclear Relationship (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) - Report on Budget Priorities Project (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) - CISAC (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) - CW - Committee on Demilitarizing Chemical Munitions and Agents, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) - Committee on Technology Leakage, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) - Computer Science and Tech Board (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) - Computer Science and Tech Board - Summary (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) - Conduct of Science (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) - Member-Electronic Mail (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) - Genetics (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) - Global Warming (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) - Global Warming - Draft IOM Human Health Section (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) - Climate (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) - Graduate Study, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) - Issues in Sciene and Tech (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) - Policy Research Briefing (Box 24, Folder 22)